86callchina.com 2010-06-25

# Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

We respect your privacy. We has created this privacy policy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to our visitors' privacy. It is our policy:

Personal Information

We do not collect any personal information about you other than that you specifically provide. When visiting the site 86callchina.com, to make a purchase and register to use certain services, you may be asked to provide your name, email, address or telephone number. 

We may use personal information to contact a purchaser and fulfill orders. We do not sell, rent, or loan any information that identifies you to third parties without your consent.

The information you post to guestbook becomes public information. we reserve the right to, but it not obligated to, refuse or delete any content in our sole discretion. 

Cookies

We may use cookies (1) to customize your visit to the our web site and your shopping experience, (2) to identify shoppers with their shopping carts, (3) to make your visit more convenient. We use cookies in a responsible manner to help our visitors, not snoop on them. You may restrict the placement of cookies on your computer, in this case you are not able to use some service normally.

Other Sites

Our site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices and the content of other sites. 

Security

The security of your personal information is very important to us. All your data are stored in areas not accessible to Web browsers, behind password protection, or offline. Access to that information is strictly controlled and limited to certain individuals within us. 

If you have any questions about our privacy policy please contact us.
